http://www.aspalliance.com/privacy.aspx

ASP.NET Tutorials » Privacy Policy  Not Logged In. Login
AspAlliance.com
Web
AspAllianceRegisterEdit My ProfileAuthor ListWrite for UsAbout AspAllianceContact UsPrivacy PolicyLink To UsAdvertiseSubscribeFree NewsletterNewsletter ArchiveRSS Syndication .NET TutorialsLearn .NETLearn WCFLearn WPFLearn ASP.NETLearn AJAXLearn SilverlightLearn Visual StudioLearn ADO.NETLearn LINQLearn C# (CSharp)Learn VB.NETLearn Web ServicesLearn ControlsLearn BizTalkLearn SharePointLearn MobileLearn SQLLearn SQL ReportingLearn Windows FormsLearn XMLLearn Crystal ReportsLearn FarPointLearn DevExpressExamplesASP.NET 2.0 ExamplesASP TutorialsLearn ASPLearn VBScriptLearn JScriptLearn SQLLearn XMLSoftware ResourcesShopping Cart EcommerceCharts and DashboardsOther ResourcesLearn JavaLearn OracleOpinion / EditorialCrystal Reports AllianceWPF ResourcesAJAX ResourcesSilverlight ResourcesFree ToolsCache ManagerSimpleCMSReviewsBook ReviewsProduct ReviewsExpert AdviceBooksASP.NET Developer's CookbookSample ChaptersBook ReviewsCommunityRegular Expressions
Privacy Statement for AspAlliance.com
AspAlliance.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate
our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information
gathering and dissemination practices for this website: AspAlliance.com.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to
administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have
to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information
(like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used
to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future
mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
This site contains links to other sites. AspAlliance.com is not
responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email
address). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out
section below.
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information
(like their email address). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see
the choice/opt-out section below.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web
site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a
cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this
Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address
email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites
in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available
to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these
areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding
to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and
alteration of the information under our control.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications
from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from
our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our
service.
You can contact us via our Feedback Page.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information
previously provided:
Update your profile
Contact us via our Feedback Page.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Steven Smith
AspAlliance.com
PO Box 1856
Kent, OH 44240
or contact us via our Feedback Page.
Community Advice: ASP |
SQL |
XML |
Regular Expressions |
Windows
©Copyright 1998-2020 ASPAlliance.com  |  Page Processed at 2020-12-11 1:29:55 AM  About ASPAlliance | Newsgroups | Advertise | Authors | Email Lists | Feedback | Link To Us | Privacy | Search
